Tony Antony

ABOUT ME

Engineer

Since 2018

A driven engineer with broad experience in the industry, with a successful track record in solving diverse Engineering problems, confident in bringing a fresh perspective to your organization and its various business problems.

EXPERIENCE

CanvasJS

June 2023 – July 2023 | Software Developer

- Worked on clientside charting library product using vanilla Javascript implemented with canvas element API of HTML
- > Created 5000+ automated testcases in a span of a week with cypress framework
- > Carried out client support activities on dedicated forum

Vualapp

Aug 2022 - April 2023 | Full-stack Developer

- Collaborated with a 2 person founding engineering team to automate the invoice aggregation procedure, making the platform a viable solution for accounting customers.
- Contributed to all aspects of product building, including development, testing, and documentation.
- > Effectively contributed to implementing modularity, scalability, and bug fixes for the existing codebase.
- > Primary stacks used include Vue, AWS (Lambda), and Supabase, with Gitlab for version control and CI/CD.
- > Implemented an event-based microservice on serverless compute, specifically AWS Lambda.
- > Facilitated the successful migration of the product between AWS accounts by transferring configurations, instances, security groups, and identity and access management, while documenting the entire procedure.
- > Helped the organization build a sustainable browser automation solution using Puppeteer/Playwright.

SIBCA Electronics Equipment

April 2019 - June 2021 | Technichal Service Engineer

- > Programmed, commissioned, and serviced Extra Low Voltage systems and Central Battery systems.
- > Communicated with clients, delivered services, and planned resources.
- > Delivered technical project documentation.
- Demonstrated hands-on experience in operating and troubleshooting various scalable electronic systems

EDUCATION

TKM College of Engineering

2014 – 2018 | Bachelor of Technlology in Electronics and Communication

NAAC Accredited Govt-Aided Engineering college under Kerala University

SKILLS

JavaScript

Expert Level

Completed 69-hour beginner to Expert JavaScript course from udemy.

ES6	Node	React	Redux		Vue			
Object Oriented Programming boolean logic								
inheritance Asynchronous JavaScript								

Other

VSCode	HTML	CSS	Git	AW:	S L	Linux serv		er
debuggin	g Lam	bda	Hosting		hell scrip		ting	
Supabase	Post	gres	SQL	CI/C	D (CLI	EC2	
S3 Clo	udflare	Secu	Security Groups IA				/PC	
Cloudwat	tomati	on P	uppet	uppeteer		Playwright		
Cypress	PI F	Fiddler Prompt			g			
Visual stu	ortoise	oise git source code manipul			nipula	tion		

CONTACT

https://tonyantony.xyz https://github.com/tonyantony300 https://github.com/tonyantony300 https://github.com/tonyantony300 https://github.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300@gmail.com/tonyantony300